[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 11, "question": "David Frost?", "question_tokens": ["David", "Frost", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 12, "answer": "I want to know this.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "know", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Frost"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "Nice to be with you.", "answer_tokens": ["Nice", "to", "be", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "Or better?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "It wouldn't be better.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "n't", "be", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "Is it easier coming when you're not a favorite?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "easier", "coming", "when", "you", "'re", "not", "a", "favorite", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "I think being the front-runner is tough.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "being", "the", "front-runner", "is", "tough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Isn't it worth paying more money?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "worth", "paying", "more", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Maybe.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin", "Obama"]}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "What is your view of Sarah Palin?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "of", "Sarah", "Palin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "My view of Sarah Palin is she is the most dynamic figure maybe in politics, even more in some ways than President Obama, who is a little more scripted than she is.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "view", "of", "Sarah", "Palin", "is", "she", "is", "the", "most", "dynamic", "figure", "maybe", "in", "politics", ",", "even", "more", "in", "some", "ways", "than", "President", "Obama", ",", "who", "is", "a", "little", "more", "scripted", "than", "she", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Is she right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Except for the use of the word, absolutely right on.", "answer_tokens": ["Except", "for", "the", "use", "of", "the", "word", ",", "absolutely", "right", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "Which word?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "word", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Blood libel.", "answer_tokens": ["Blood", "libel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Why do you do that unless it's inherently, you think it's wrong?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "do", "that", "unless", "it", "'s", "inherently", ",", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Because you know what the media is going to do.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "you", "know", "what", "the", "media", "is", "going", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Would you have ever done -- I don't know if you ever did -- but what you have ever done a website of your own which had crosshairs aimed at political targets?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "ever", "done", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "you", "ever", "did", "--", "but", "what", "you", "have", "ever", "done", "a", "website", "of", "your", "own", "which", "had", "crosshairs", "aimed", "at", "political", "targets", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ":", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "WDT", "VBD", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Not if I had thought about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "if", "I", "had", "thought", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Given the furor, though, do you think it would now be prudent for politicians to not do that?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "the", "furor", ",", "though", ",", "do", "you", "think", "it", "would", "now", "be", "prudent", "for", "politicians", "to", "not", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Of course it would.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "it", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "Is Sarah Palin too polarizing to win against Barack Obama?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "Sarah", "Palin", "too", "polarizing", "to", "win", "against", "Barack", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "You know, it depends.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "depends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "But against President Obama?", "question_tokens": ["But", "against", "President", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "It depends on the job he does.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "depends", "on", "the", "job", "he", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Would you be more tempted to run if she wasn't?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "be", "more", "tempted", "to", "run", "if", "she", "was", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RBR", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Maybe the opposite.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "the", "opposite", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Maybe the opposite because my one chance, if I have a chance, is that I'm considered a moderate Republican.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "the", "opposite", "because", "my", "one", "chance", ",", "if", "I", "have", "a", "chance", ",", "is", "that", "I", "'m", "considered", "a", "moderate", "Republican", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Do you agree on some of the outpourings of the Tea Party bordering on bigotry?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", "on", "some", "of", "the", "outpourings", "of", "the", "Tea", "Party", "bordering", "on", "bigotry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "I find some of the outpourings of all of these movements bordering on extremist.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "find", "some", "of", "the", "outpourings", "of", "all", "of", "these", "movements", "bordering", "on", "extremist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Isn't that bad for American society?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "bad", "for", "American", "society", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "So isn't there a real inherent danger?", "question_tokens": ["So", "is", "n't", "there", "a", "real", "inherent", "danger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "No, I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Why are you creating two parties?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "creating", "two", "parties", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "No, I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["State of the Union"]}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "If you were him, what would you be saying?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "him", ",", "what", "would", "you", "be", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "If I were him, I would be saying the State of the Union is strong, which I do think it is.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "were", "him", ",", "I", "would", "be", "saying", "the", "State", "of", "the", "Union", "is", "strong", ",", "which", "I", "do", "think", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "What should he be saying?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "he", "be", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "First of all he should be saying it's strong.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", "he", "should", "be", "saying", "it", "'s", "strong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Is it eight?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "eight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Would you raise taxes?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "raise", "taxes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Can you honestly say that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "honestly", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "But is it as simple as that, really?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "it", "as", "simple", "as", "that", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "We collect taxes.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "collect", "taxes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Did you know Bernie Madoff?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "Bernie", "Madoff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "I did not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bernie Madoff"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "When you were mayor, you had no inkling of what he was up to?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "were", "mayor", ",", "you", "had", "no", "inkling", "of", "what", "he", "was", "up", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Rudy, the war in Afghanistan isn't working, is it?", "question_tokens": ["Rudy", ",", "the", "war", "in", "Afghanistan", "is", "n't", "working", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "It hasn't come to the result we want yet.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "has", "n't", "come", "to", "the", "result", "we", "want", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "If I invite you back in 2015, do you honestly think that there will be any kind of tangible victory in Afghanistan?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "invite", "you", "back", "in", "2015", ",", "do", "you", "honestly", "think", "that", "there", "will", "be", "any", "kind", "of", "tangible", "victory", "in", "Afghanistan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "CD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "I think there could be, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "could", "be", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2015"], "LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Or Iraq?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "Iraq", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Probably all three.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "all", "three", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Using the same yardstick of argument that you used with Saddam Hussein?", "question_tokens": ["Using", "the", "same", "yardstick", "of", "argument", "that", "you", "used", "with", "Saddam", "Hussein", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "I think it would be a mistake right now to invade Iran.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "would", "be", "a", "mistake", "right", "now", "to", "invade", "Iran", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Saddam Hussein"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Korea", "North Korea"]}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "And I'm assuming North Korea presumably?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "'m", "assuming", "North", "Korea", "presumably", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "North Korea is a different situation which we can talk about different things involving North Korea.", "answer_tokens": ["North", "Korea", "is", "a", "different", "situation", "which", "we", "can", "talk", "about", "different", "things", "involving", "North", "Korea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Do you believe fundamentally that America should be doing more of these trips?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "fundamentally", "that", "America", "should", "be", "doing", "more", "of", "these", "trips", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Absolutely, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Would you meet with Hezbollah, with al Qaeda?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "meet", "with", "Hezbollah", ",", "with", "al", "Qaeda", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "It would depend on what could be accomplished.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "depend", "on", "what", "could", "be", "accomplished", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hezbollah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "But as a principle, you believe it is probably time that America talked more to its enemies?", "question_tokens": ["But", "as", "a", "principle", ",", "you", "believe", "it", "is", "probably", "time", "that", "America", "talked", "more", "to", "its", "enemies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "JJR", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "If America has the objective of obtaining advantages from it.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "America", "has", "the", "objective", "of", "obtaining", "advantages", "from", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Would you meet this group again?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "meet", "this", "group", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Given that Pakistan and countries like that are clearly unstable and in possession of a number of weapons, is this really the right time for America to be downgrading?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "that", "Pakistan", "and", "countries", "like", "that", "are", "clearly", "unstable", "and", "in", "possession", "of", "a", "number", "of", "weapons", ",", "is", "this", "really", "the", "right", "time", "for", "America", "to", "be", "downgrading", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "I didn't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "JJR", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Is America as susceptible now to another attack like that as it was then, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "America", "as", "susceptible", "now", "to", "another", "attack", "like", "that", "as", "it", "was", "then", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "IULIANI: Probably less, for the simple fact that they're looking for it more.", "answer_tokens": ["IULIANI", ":", "Probably", "less", ",", "for", "the", "simple", "fact", "that", "they", "'re", "looking", "for", "it", "more", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Are you surprised, in a good way, that there hasn't been another huge attack on American mainland in the last decade?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "surprised", ",", "in", "a", "good", "way", ",", "that", "there", "has", "n't", "been", "another", "huge", "attack", "on", "American", "mainland", "in", "the", "last", "decade", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Very surprised.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "surprised", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Denny Young", "Bill Simon"]}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "How did you hear what had happened?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "hear", "what", "had", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "One of the police officers that was with me came up to my counsel, Denny Young, who was having breakfast with me, and Bill Simon was the third person.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "police", "officers", "that", "was", "with", "me", "came", "up", "to", "my", "counsel", ",", "Denny", "Young", ",", "who", "was", "having", "breakfast", "with", "me", ",", "and", "Bill", "Simon", "was", "the", "third", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "What are you now thinking?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "now", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "IULIANI: I'm thinking how do I get air support for the city.", "answer_tokens": ["IULIANI", ":", "I", "'m", "thinking", "how", "do", "I", "get", "air", "support", "for", "the", "city", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "RBR", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Why did you say that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I thought if I said a number like 12,000, it would -- it would just create even more fear, more shock, possibly even panic.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "if", "I", "said", "a", "number", "like", "12,000", ",", "it", "would", "--", "it", "would", "just", "create", "even", "more", "fear", ",", "more", "shock", ",", "possibly", "even", "panic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "If you had been the president?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "been", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Being the president is very different, because there is a whole obligation.", "answer_tokens": ["Being", "the", "president", "is", "very", "different", ",", "because", "there", "is", "a", "whole", "obligation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Why would you do that, Rudy?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "do", "that", ",", "Rudy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "My staff used to then tease me and say oh, gee, we have a little more Anthrax.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "staff", "used", "to", "then", "tease", "me", "and", "say", "oh", ",", "gee", ",", "we", "have", "a", "little", "more", "Anthrax", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rudy?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "How did you take that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "take", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "That's not an official position.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "an", "official", "position", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Is there ever a day when you don't think about 9/11?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "ever", "a", "day", "when", "you", "do", "n't", "think", "about", "9/11", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "No, not a day.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "a", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "How did you feel when the 9/11 Health Care Bill was being debated and there were Republicans who did not want that to go through?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "the", "9/11", "Health", "Care", "Bill", "was", "being", "debated", "and", "there", "were", "Republicans", "who", "did", "not", "want", "that", "to", "go", "through", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "DT", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "I was annoyed with using it as a political device.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "annoyed", "with", "using", "it", "as", "a", "political", "device", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["9/11 Health Care Bill"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "-- that transcend politics?", "question_tokens": ["--", "that", "transcend", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "thought that one transcends politics.", "answer_tokens": ["thought", "that", "one", "transcends", "politics", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "What do you think America learned about itself after 9/11?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "America", "learned", "about", "itself", "after", "9/11", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "That we're very resilient, that we can take the worst attack in our history and we can come back from it.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "we", "'re", "very", "resilient", ",", "that", "we", "can", "take", "the", "worst", "attack", "in", "our", "history", "and", "we", "can", "come", "back", "from", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "What was it like being knighted by the queen of England?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "being", "knighted", "by", "the", "queen", "of", "England", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "It was fascinating.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "fascinating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Did you regularly dress up in women's clothes?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "regularly", "dress", "up", "in", "women", "'s", "clothes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "I did it two or three times as part of --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "it", "two", "or", "three", "times", "as", "part", "of", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "Would you have rather been a great movie star, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "rather", "been", "a", "great", "movie", "star", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "No, I think I -- I had a much better career than I ever expected.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "I", "--", "I", "had", "a", "much", "better", "career", "than", "I", "ever", "expected", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "How is marriage the third time around?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "marriage", "the", "third", "time", "around", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "It's fabulous.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "fabulous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "You don't feel good about it, because it affects your family.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "feel", "good", "about", "it", ",", "because", "it", "affects", "your", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "JJR", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Did you have any big regrets about the impact of your political life on your family life?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "any", "big", "regrets", "about", "the", "impact", "of", "your", "political", "life", "on", "your", "family", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "Sure, I guess you'd wished if you had gone back, you had done it better, done it differently.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "I", "guess", "you", "'d", "wished", "if", "you", "had", "gone", "back", ",", "you", "had", "done", "it", "better", ",", "done", "it", "differently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "What would you say has been the best day of your life?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "has", "been", "the", "best", "day", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "Probably the same day.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "the", "same", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "Out of an attempt to really demoralize and destabilize America, oddly unity and strength came out of that?", "question_tokens": ["Out", "of", "an", "attempt", "to", "really", "demoralize", "and", "destabilize", "America", ",", "oddly", "unity", "and", "strength", "came", "out", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NNP", ",", "RB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "Would you come back nearer the time of the anniversary?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "come", "back", "nearer", "the", "time", "of", "the", "anniversary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "Yeah, I will.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110124pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "Is homosexuality a sin in your eyes?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "homosexuality", "a", "sin", "in", "your", "eyes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "Yes, I've always believed, Piers, the scripture shows that it's a sin.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'ve", "always", "believed", ",", "Piers", ",", "the", "scripture", "shows", "that", "it", "'s", "a", "sin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]